Guide to the American Newspaper Repository Collection, 1852-2004 RL.10057
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Nowy Swiat (New York), 1944-1945, 1951-1954, 72
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1952 Jan.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1165)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1952 May-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1232)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1952 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1164)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1953 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1166)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1953 May-July; wrapped bundle (Box 1171)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1953 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1239)
    [Note: Badly damaged]
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1954 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1167)
  - Nowy Swiat (New York), 1954 May-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1246)
- Occident, The, 1885-1895, 73
  - Occident, The, 1885 April 17- 1888 Sept.; bound volume (Volume 5631)
  - Occident, The, 1888 Oct. 12-1891 Sept. 25; bound volume (Volume 5634)
  - Occident, The, 1891 Oct. 1-1893 Sept. 6; bound volume (Volume 5632)
  - Occident, The, 1893 Sept. 29-1895 Sept. 6; bound volume (Volume 5633)
- Our Sunday Afternoon, 1889, 74
  - Our Sunday Afternoon, 1889 May 18; wrapped bundle (Box 1951)
- Patrie, 1896-1897, 75
  - Patrie, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
- Patryota (Philadelphia), 1950-1955, 76
  - Patryota (Philadelphia), 1950 Dec.-1952 Nov.; wrapped bundle (Box 1403)
  - Patryota (Philadelphia), 1953 Jan.-1955 Jan. 14; wrapped bundle (Box 1403)
- Pelley's Weekly (Asheville, N.C.), 1934-1936, 77
  - Pelley's Weekly (Asheville, N.C.), 1934 Aug. 29-1936 May 13; volume (Volume 5706)
  - Pelley's Weekly (Asheville, N.C.), 1936 May 20-Nov. 11; volume (Volume 5705)
  - Pelley's Weekly (Asheville, N.C.), 1936 Nov. 18-25; volume (Volume 5707)
- Polish American Journal (Scranton, PA), 1950-1955, 78
  - Polish American Journal (Scranton, PA), 1950 Nov.-1952 Dec. 27; wrapped bundle (Box 1391)
  - Polish American Journal (Scranton, PA), 1952 Jan.-1953 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1392)
  - Polish American Journal (Scranton, PA), 1954; wrapped bundle (Box 1390)
  - Polish American Journal (Scranton, PA), 1955 June-July 23; wrapped bundle (Box 1390)
- Post-Standard (Syracuse, NY), 1963, 79
  - Post-Standard (Syracuse, NY), 1963; loose newspaper (Box 1738)
- Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1942-1946, 80
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1942 Jan.-June; volume (Volume 6725)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1942 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 6742)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1942 Nov.-1945 May; volume (Volume 5708)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1943 Jan.-June; volume (Volume 6746)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1943 July-Dec.; volume (Volume 6728)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1944 Jan. 1-June 24; volume (Volume 6727)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1944 July-Dec.; volume (Volume 6745)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1945 Jan.-June; volume (Volume 6741)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1945 July-Dec.; volume (Volume 5682)
  - Pour la Victoire (New York, N.Y.), 1946 Jan. 5-May 11; volume (Volume 6726)
- Robotnik Polski (New York), 1942-1967, 81
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1942 May 17-1951 Apr. 23; wrapped bundle (Box 1395)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1946 Aug. 25-1951 Sept. 23; wrapped bundle (Box 1395)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1952 Mar. 9-1953 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1395)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1954; wrapped bundle (Box 1115)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1955; wrapped bundle (Box 1055)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1956; wrapped bundle (Box 1396)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1957-1958; wrapped bundle (Box 1113)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1959-1960; wrapped bundle (Box 1397)
  - Robotnik Polski (New York), 1961 Feb.-1967 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1114)
- Ruskii Golos (New York), 1930, 1949, 82
  - Ruskii Golos (New York), 1930 Apr. 15; 16; wrapped bundle (Box 1383)
  - Ruskii Golos (New York), 1949 Mar. 17-July 25; wrapped bundle (Box 1383)
- Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1964-1969, 83
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1964 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1440)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1965 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1447)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1965 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1446)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1966 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1445)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1966 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1444)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1967 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1448)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1967 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1439)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1968 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1443)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1968 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1442)
  - Russkaia Zhizn (San Francisco), 1969 Jan.-May; wrapped bundle (Box 1441)
- San Francisco Chronicle, 1917, 84
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1917 Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4574)
- Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1924-1964, 85
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1924 Aug.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5653)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1925 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5657)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1925 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5650)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1926 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5663)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1926 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5658)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1927 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5652)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1927 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5645)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1928 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1734)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1928 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5661)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1929 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1735)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1929 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5662)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1930 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5649)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1930 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5655)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1931 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5664)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1931 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5656)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1932 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5660)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1932 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5659)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1933 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5648)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1933 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5647)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1934 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5651)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1934 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5644)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1935; bound volume (Volume 5654)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1935 Jan- Apr.; bound volume (Volume 5646)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1936 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4780)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1936 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4548)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1937 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4778)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1937 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4779)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1938 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4771)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1938 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4769)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1939 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4627)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1939 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4770)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1940 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4777)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1940 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4613)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1941 Jan.-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4614)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1952 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4618)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1952 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4603)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1953 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4782)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1953 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4783)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1953 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4774)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1954 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4784)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1954 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4767)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1954 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4768)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1955 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4625)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1955 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4621)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1955 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4623)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1956 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4622)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1956 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4766)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1956 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4775)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1957 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4616)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1957 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4619)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1957 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4781)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1958 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 1620)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1958 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4773)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1958 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4626)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1959 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4772)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1959 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4776)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1959 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4612)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1960 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4606)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1960 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4605)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1960 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4611)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1961 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4607)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1961 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4624)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1961 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4608)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1962 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4610)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1962 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4617)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1962-May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4615)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1963 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4765)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1963 May-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 4609)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1963 Sept.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4604)
  - Saturday Review of Literature, The, 1964 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4764)
- Seattle Daily Times, The, 1961, 86
  - Seattle Daily Times, The, 1961; loose newspaper (Box 1871-1872)
- Siècle, 1898, 87
  - Siècle, 1898 Mar.-Apr.; volume in box (Box 1867)
- Sloboda (Chicago), 1954-1973, 88
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1954 Oct. 27-1955 Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1158)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1955 Apr. 13-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1125)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1956; wrapped bundle (Box 1156)
    [Note: Missing #210-213]
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1957; wrapped bundle (Box 528)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1958; wrapped bundle (Box 486)
    [Note: Missing no. 264, 270]
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1959 Jan.-Dec. 10; wrapped bundle (Box 475)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1960; wrapped bundle (Box 473)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1961; wrapped bundle (Box 529)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1962; wrapped bundle (Box 514)
    [Note: Missing no. 436, 439, 442, 447]
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1963; wrapped bundle (Box 1127)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1964; wrapped bundle (Box 474)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1965 Jan. 10-Dec. 20; wrapped bundle (Box 1123)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1966; wrapped bundle (Box 461)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1967; wrapped bundle (Box 499)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1968; wrapped bundle (Box 1126)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1969; wrapped bundle (Box 1124)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1970; wrapped bundle (Box 1157)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1971; wrapped bundle (Box 1122)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1972; wrapped bundle (Box 463)
  - Sloboda (Chicago), 1973; wrapped bundle (Box 462)
- Solia (Detroit), 1954-1972, 89
  - Solia (Detroit), 1954-1960; wrapped bundle (Box 1393)
  - Solia (Detroit), 1961-1965; wrapped bundle (Box 1152)
  - Solia (Detroit), 1966-1967; wrapped bundle (Box 1373)
  - Solia (Detroit), 1968 Jan.-1971 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1394)
  - Solia (Detroit), 1972; wrapped bundle (Box 1152)
- Street Railway Journal, The, 1884-1908, 90
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1884 Nov.-1885 Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4682)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1885 Nov.-1886 Oct.; bound volume (Volume 5239)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1886 Nov.-1887 Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4678)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1888; bound volume (Volume 5454)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1889; bound volume (Volume 5455)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1890; bound volume (Volume 4679)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1891; bound volume (Volume 5512)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1892; volume in box (Box 1681)
    [Note: Includes Index to vol. VIII]
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1893; bound volume (Volume 5453)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1894; bound volume (Volume 5237)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1895; bound volume (Volume 5513)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1896; volume in box (Box 1680)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1897; volume in box (Box 1679)
    [Note: Includes Index to vol. XIII]
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1898; bound volume (Volume 5509)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1899; bound volume (Volume 5457)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1900; bound volume (Volume 5452)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1901; bound volume (Volume 5510)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1901 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4683)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1902 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4684)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1902 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4664)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1903; bound volume (Volume 5511)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1903; bound volume (Volume 5240)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1904 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4670)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1904 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4666)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1905 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4671)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1905 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4668)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1906 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4677)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1906 June-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4674)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1907 Jan-June; bound volume (Volume 5456)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1907 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4675)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, 1908 Jan.-May; bound volume (Volume 4672)
  - Street Railway Journal, The, General Index, 1884 Oct.-1903 Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4669)
- Sunday School Times, The, 1900-1908, 91
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1900; bound volume (Volume 6014)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1901; bound volume (Volume 5999)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1902; bound volume (Volume 5998)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1903; bound volume (Volume 6002)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1904; bound volume (Volume 6001)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1905; bound volume (Volume 5995)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1906; bound volume (Volume 6004)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1907; bound volume (Volume 6003)
  - Sunday School Times, The, 1908; bound volume (Volume 5991)
- Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1936-1938, 92
  - Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1936 Jan. 12-June 28; volume (Volume 6744)
  - Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1936 July 5-1937 Jan. 3; volume (Volume 5685)
  - Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1937 Jan. 10-June 27; volume (Volume 5686)
  - Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1937 July 4-Dec. 26; volume (Volume 5688)
  - Sunday Worker (New York, N.Y.), 1938 Jan. 2-June 26; volume (Volume 5689)
- Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1920-1971, 93
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1920; bound volume (Volume 5789)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1921 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5800)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1921 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5793)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1922 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5796)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1922 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5801)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1923 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5787)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1923 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5788)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1924 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5791)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1924 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5792)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1925 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 5795)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1925 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 5799)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1926 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1586)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1926 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1612)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1927 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1659)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1927 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1601)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1928 Jan.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1660)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1929 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1648)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1929 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1658)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1930 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1589)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1930 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1703)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1931 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1609)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1931 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1702)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1932 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1714)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1932 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1716)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1933 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1712)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1933 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1720)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1934 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1721)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1934 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1721)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1934 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1717)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1934 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1629)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1935 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1715)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1935 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1710)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1936 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1718)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1937 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1713)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1937 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1719)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1938 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1707)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1938 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1705)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1938 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1711)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1939 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1709)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1939 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1708)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1940 Jan.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1653)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1940 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1652)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1940 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1651)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1941 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1615)
    [Note: Missing Mar. 24, 25]
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1941 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1608)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1942 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1655)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1942 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1654)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1943 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1647)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1943 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1588)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1944 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1587)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1944 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1610)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1945 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1646)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1945 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1726)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1946 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1649)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1946 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1650)
    [Note: Missing July 1]
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1947 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1701)
    [Note: Missing Feb. 17-24]
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1947 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1613)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1948 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1606)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 5, 7, 8]
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1948 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1596)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1949 [No month specified]; wrapped bundle (Box 1644)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1949 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1645)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1950 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1614)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1950 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1590)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1951 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1607)
    [Note: Missing June 14, 18]
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1951 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1591)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1952 Jan.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1240)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1952 May-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1704)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1953 Jan.-Feb. 21; wrapped bundle (Box 1604)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1953 Feb. 24-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1603)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1953 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1200)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1954 Jan.-May 28; wrapped bundle (Box 1218)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1954 June-[1955] Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1202)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1954 June-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1611)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1955 May-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1199)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1956 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1602)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1956 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1604)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1956 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1605)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1956 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1717)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1957 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1618)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1957 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1621)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1958 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1620)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1958 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1619)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1959 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1226)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1959 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1219)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1959 June 5-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1245)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1959 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1657)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1959 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1656)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1960 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1656)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1960 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1657)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1960 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1652)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1960 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1600)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1961 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1600)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1961 Mar.-May; wrapped bundle (Box 1599)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1961 June-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1593)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1961 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1592)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1962 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1216)
  - Svoboda (New York, Jersey City), 1962 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1230)